// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Zwölf:12::Zwanzing:?",
    answer: "20",
    options: [
      "21",
      "22",
      "20",
      "11"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many colors does a rainbow have?",
    answer: "sieben",
    options: [
      "acht",
      "elf",
      "sechs",
      "sieben"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How would you wish 'Good morning' to your friend?",
    answer: "Guten Morgen",
    options: [
      "Guten Nachmittag",
      "Guten Nacht",
      "Guten Morgen",
      "Entschuldigung"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Fill in the blanks: 654 =  ___ hundert ___und___",
    answer: "Sechs, vier, fünfzig",
    options: [
      "Sieben, vier, fünfzig",
      "Sechs, fünf, vierzig",
      "Sechs, vier, fünfzehn",
      "Sechs, vier, fünfzig"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What will be your reply to 'Danke!'?",
    answer: "Bitte",
    options: [
      "Bitte schöne",
      "Bitte",
      "Danke schön",
      "Es tut mir leid"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Translate in German: They play cricket.",
    answer: "Sie spielen Kricket.",
    options: [
      "Sie spielt Kricket.",
      "Sie spiele Kricket.",
      "Sie spielst Kricket.",
      "Sie spielen Kricket."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Fragen:Ask::?:Reply",
    answer: "Antworten",
    options: [
      "Arbeiten",
      "Antworten",
      "Schreiben",
      "Machen"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the antonym to cry in German?",
    answer: "Lachen",
    options: [
      "Lachen",
      "Laughen",
      "Lernen",
      "Laufen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Translate into German: We have car.",
    answer: "Wir haben Auto.",
    options: [
      "Wir habe Auto.",
      "Wir hat Auto.",
      "Ihr haben Auto.",
      "Wir haben Auto."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Translate into English: Du bist Student",
    answer: "You are student.",
    options: [
      "I am student.",
      "She is student.",
      "You are student.",
      "He is student."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How would you say 'years old' while telling your age in German?",
    answer: "Jahre Alt",
    options: [
      "Jahre Alt",
      "Jahr Alt",
      "Jahre Neu",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Die:Woche::Das:?",
    answer: "Wochenende",
    options: [
      "Tag",
      "Montag",
      "Sonntag",
      "Wochenende"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is the saucer paired with?",
    answer: "die Tasse",
    options: [
      "das Glas",
      "die Flasche",
      "die Tasse",
      "der Löffel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is your relation with son of your mother?",
    answer: "Bruder",
    options: [
      "Bruder",
      "Tochter",
      "Schwester",
      "Freund"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Liabrary:Bibliothek::Store:?",
    answer: "Geschäft",
    options: [
      "Flughafen",
      "Markt",
      "Bahnhof",
      "Geschäft"
    ]
  },
];
